Oh
Sorry Akane hmm, I met a girl I like
Hmm well now that I think about it. He has been pretty cold toward me lately
Huh? Your boyfriend dumped you for some girl in an MMO?
That's hysterical! Who in the world does that?
Please, Momo, that's not helping things.
Wait, unless I'm mistaken, you were playing a computer game together, is that the one?
Yep, that's the one.
Sheesh, who knew homewrecking went down in games, too?
Hey, Akane! This game's pretty sweet, you should play with me!
Really? What kind of game is it?
It's an MMO! Just came out!
It was fairly obvious that he had a knack for playing games, but I never thought he'd cheat on me with a girl in the game.
Not to mention this last message he sent me.
Is this guy heartless or what? I mean, what are you supposed to say to that?
Seems to me breaking up was the right move.
I know you're hurting, but this pain won't last forever, Akane.
I've got classes this afternoon, so I'm heading out.
But one more thing, don't let the doom and gloom consume you. Make time for class!
Staying cooped up will make things worse, okay?
I'll be fine. It's not like I'm gonna die just because I got dumped. Life will go on. I can't cut too many classes. And I need to get a part-time job soon.
Ugh. I wonder if he picked up that equipment yet.
I was never into games before.
But if it meant that we could have fun together, that was good enough for me.
Oh, he's already unfriended me. Well, that was fast.
I really wish I could have fun together.
But if it meant that we could have fun together, that was good enough for me.
Oh, he's already unfriended me. Well, that was fast. I really wish I hadn't bought all these items if we were just gonna break up.
I bought 3,000 yen worth of in-game clothes. All that's left is this character I've leveled up for nothing.
Strike! Strike! Strike! Strike!
Power!
Hero!
Um...
Hmm?
Well, that was fast.
I really wish I hadn't bought all these items if we were just gonna break up.
I bought 3,000 yen worth of in-game clothes.
All that's left is this character I've leveled up for nothing.
Strike! Strike! Strike! Strike!
Power!
ERO!
Um...
Hmm?
Huh?
Who's this Afro guy in the Gnome Mask again?
He seems familiar.
Ahh!
He's my guildmate, Yamada.
Oh.
…
The Joy of thevant
Yeah, it's him, all right.
Just as aloof and unsociable as I thought he was.
Seriously, who takes two whole minutes to write hello and yes?
Hmm?
Hmm.
Seems he's quite the hardcore game addict.
I'm not here for that.
See, I'm out here doing some hunting because I was annoyed my boyfriend dumped me yesterday.
Can you believe it?
Apparently it's thanks to this very game that I got cheated on in the first place.
Like, what's up with that?
Oh.
Is that so?
No, I don't think I will.
Since I was here first, that obviously means you should cede this hunting ground to me and be on your way.
I was told that's hunting ground etiquette, good sir.
I'm sure this won't interest you at all, but my breakup shattered my heart into pieces.
So I'm using this hunting ground as the perfect outlet for my stress.
Please try for the profit stone in some other channel, because there is no way I am ever giving up this spot!
Not good.
I was so annoyed that I lashed out at this afro-wearing stranger.
Actually, having heard you out...
You're right.
I hate you, Yamada!
I am so not leaving here until he logs out!
This is why I can't stand Gamer Guys!
Huh?
An event?
There will be avatars and gifts for all the attendees.
Hey, that's not far from here.
Akane, let's stay together forever.
Okay.
Sorry...
I met someone else I like...
Akane, let's stay together forever.
Okay.
Sorry. I met someone else I like in that game when we were playing together.
And the thing is, she says she likes me too.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, I get it. You're already going out with her, aren't you?
I wonder if they'll be going to this event together too.
Dang it.
I can't just go down as the one who got dumped.
Hey, Akane!
You showed up for class. Got that guy out of your system?
Momo, hi.
Hey, think you can come shopping with me later? I need to put an outfit together.
Huh? You planning on going out somewhere?
Yeah, actually. I'm attending an event.
Should be a good time, and I bet you know who will make an appearance as well.
Meaning I'll have a chance to watch him wallow in regret when he sees how gorgeous I've become.
Okay. We call that not being over our ex.
This event wouldn't be for that game, would it?
Of course it is.
What else would it be for?
And that being the case, there's a very high chance he'll be there.
Girl, that's sad.
Say whatever you will.
That's the plan.
Watch. I'll make him regret ditching me for a gamer girl.
He'll kick himself for dumping me.
Just watch.
If it's the last thing I do, I'm gonna make him regret it.
To all of you attending the Forest of Savior Autumn Festival today,
we'd like to extend a big thank you.
The pin code you received at the gate will expire at the end of December.
So please keep that in mind as you continue to the event.
This event is way livelier than I thought it'd be.
And I seriously underestimated the amount of people who'd show.
Wait. It just dawned on me.
Am I headed straight for bankruptcy this month over this?
Still, it's sort of wild that all the attendees here enjoy playing the same game.
Although there seems to be more guys than girls.
It's all so fascinating.
I wonder what kind of characters they play.
Takuma!
You wanna move up front?
Sure. Come on.
Wait. Come back!
What the?
No, no.
That was so dumb.
I wanna disappear.
This is all just
making me wanna cry.
Are you okay?
Whoa, what a hottie!
Yes, I'm totally fine.
I didn't accidentally bump into you by any chance, did I?
Well, yeah.
I'm so sorry.
I kind of spaced out and turned into a major klutz.
I mean, I was deep in thought.
Things have been a bit rough for me lately, so...
I really wasn't paying attention to where I was going.
Oh.
Is that so?
Sorry about that.
What's it to you, right?
Right.
Yeah.
I'm not interested.
Hmm?
That line...
Someone said the same thing to me recently.
Hmm?
Yamada?
Could you be Afro Yamada?
I'm sorry, do I know you?
Have we met, or...
Well, you see...
We, uh...
Huh?
Does he really not remember?
I'm sure I got a sense of Afro-deja vu.
Was I wrong?
It can't be a coincidence, can it?
Although, that skeptical glare doesn't inspire confidence.
Did I get the wrong guy?
Sorry for the misunder...
What?
Takuma, and his new girlfriend?
I wasn't expecting to see you here.
Takuma!
Hey, what a coincidence!
You're Mr. Yamada, right?
It's you, right, Mr. Yamada?
Who is this?
Are you kidding me?
He's only an insanely famous pro gamer, is all!
Oh, cool!
Right?
He's the best!
How did I not know you played fast, Mr. Yamada?
I'm a huge fan of your work!
I'm always watching your videos,
so this is, like, one of the coolest things I ever have in my young life!
It's unbelievable!
Are you a famous person?
Well...
Locally, I guess.
Fancy seeing you!
Are you here, Takuma?
You came here on a date, too?
When'd you get here, Akane?
Hey, I didn't see you.
Excuse me!
I've been here all along!
What are you doing in a place like this?
I do play the game, too,
so what's so strange about me being here?
It's just...
isn't being here alone...
As I said,
I'm on a date,
and this handsome fella is my boyfriend!
I'm not her boyfriend.
Please, I'm begging you,
can you find it in your heart
to show me a warrior's mercy
and play along?
Are you for real?
Think of it as showing a lost soul
a little compassion.
What?
Maybe you'd like this!
It's a perk I got for attending the event!
Take it!
Seriously?
You sure?
This is a pin coat for the Prophet Stone.
It's a super rare power-up.
It is, huh?
I'm her boyfriend.
My boyfriend!
How could this have happened?
I've been following you for three years
like the dutiful fan I am,
and I've never once received a reply.
I'm so bitter!
Takuma!
Victory!
Not what I pictured,
but his bitterness is oh so sweet,
so I'll take it.
I'm so bitter!
Come on, Takuma.
Watch your up!
Eddie!
Takuma!
Welcome!
Come in!
What do you even call this feeling
washing over me right now?
It's like I won the battle,
but lost the war in the process.
From the looks of things,
you didn't even win the battle.
You're all for two.
I knew it!
You have to be Afro, Yamada.
You got me.
By the way,
can I go home now?
Yep, that's Yamada.
Would it kill you to keep me company?
I really don't want to be alone right now!
Whoa!
That girl...
She was a real knockout.
Who now?
Takuma's girlfriend.
Who's Takuma?
My ex!
You know this already!
I told you about him in the game, chat!
Oh...
Now it's clicking.
You're that inept paladin, huh?
You just put that together?
Well,
it's a miracle that I realized it at all.
Welcome!
The truth is,
today I got all dressed up
to flaunt myself around the event
and make him regret dumping me.
But...
I didn't plan on having to see them together like that.
That's rough stuff.
Since we're gonna be here a while,
would you mind if I ordered another Coke?
Be my guest!
It's my pleasure!
I'm starting to get drained.
By the way,
about what Takuma said before,
what exactly is a pro gamer?
There's someone who gets paid by sponsors
to play games, I guess.
Sponsors?
For real?
Yeah, that's how it works.
Then you're getting paid to play FOSS, too?
That's just a break for me.
I mainly play FPS games.
Oh?
And those would be...
Uh, don't worry about it.
Hmm.
Don't you think you're a little bit too cold, Yamada?
You won't be popular with the girls acting like that.
You're right, I'm not.
I've never even had a girlfriend.
Huh?
What?
No way!
But you just said girls wouldn't like my attitude.
Never mind that, you're missing the point!
With your good looks,
how can you not be in high demand?
Well, honestly,
I'm not interested
in the whole romance thing.
Oh my.
What a waste of a pretty face.
Gaming is just more fun for me.
Wow.
I suppose romance isn't always sunshine and rainbows either.
Me getting cheated on in the game
should be plenty proof of that.
Must suck.
It does suck.
Uh-oh.
I feel tears coming on.
Pardon me a sec.
I need to use the ladies' room.
Huh?
My clothes are all dirty.
It must have happened when I tripped earlier.
Oh, great.
I scraped my leg, too.
I wish I hadn't gone to that event.
If I knew I was gonna end up feeling like this,
I would have steered clear.
Wait a second.
Where'd he go?
Don't tell me he ditched me.
I wouldn't put it past him.
He was just dying to go home.
Not that it matters, I guess.
He was only sticking around
because I forced him to.
Better get used to it.
Being alone's gonna be my new normal.
Are you okay?
Uh...
Why are you looking at me like that?
So, would you mind taking a seat for a minute?
Where did those come from?
The band-aids?
I went out and picked them up real quick.
Crap.
It's sticking.
I'm just gonna put it on.
You went out to buy these for me?
I got worried once I noticed the blood coming from your ankle, so...
So that made you rush to get them?
Well...
That and...
I drank like three cokes, you know.
Yamada!
I'll treat you to anything!
But I wanna go home now.
We're so good at drink tonight!
Uh...
Um...
May we place an order, please?
Yep, you got it!
Tani's scouting the area, so let's change it up.
We can focus on the enemies in front.
Might be able to wreck him some kills.
My head hurts.
The next map in particular.
Is that...
Yeah, someone's talking.
I told you, I'm not turning on my camera.
Who is it?
This is getting old.
Hey, uh...
My bad.
I'm gonna go AFK.
Be right back.
I don't know what to do, but I don't know what to do, but I don't know what to do, but I don't know what to do.
These hairstyles being free is great and all, but none of them are cute.
You can only get the most appealing ones from loot boxes. Fat chance I'd ever win one, though.
What? They also sell them for a fixed price? Not as good as the loot boxes, but cuter than the defaults.
I see. You can acquire them this way to show off some personality at least.
I bought the cutest one I could find at a fixed price!
Huh?
We all had the same exact thought.